Cinderella
Cinderella's sister
Cinderella's Sister
Episode 10
No, we'll leave it there for one more day.
It'll only take us a day to bring it back and leaving it there another day won't spoil the wine.
I'll find a different method by tomorrow.
Just leave the container, don't touch it and go.
I'll be hanging up.
What are you doing in this office?
Jeong Woo, please call Hyo Seon for me.
There is something I have to ask Hyo Seon.
Those clients at the Japanese hotel...
You know, the one with the son, who invited Hyo Seon home because her son liked her.
I'd like to find out if she still keeps in touch with her.
No, there's no need to ask.
Get yourself together.
You shouldn't be doing this here. Let's go.
Condolences
How come you and I already have to greet each other like this?
I have nothing to say to you.
Aigoo, Brother-in-law.
How do I live?
How do I live without Joon Soo's dad?
Aigoo, poor man.
What is this bolt from the blue?
Aigoo, you poor thing!
What did I tell you long ago?
I said you need to be careful about who you welcome into your family!
Aigoo, Honey!
Your aunt has come!
The aunt that you loved so much has come!
What are you doing wherever you are?
How could you die and go at such a young age?
Aigoo, Joon Soo's father!
Aigoo, Joon Soo loved you so much!
What are you doing wherever you are?!
Hyo Seon.
Oppa.
I'm really in big trouble.
No matter how much I drink,
I don't get drunk.
No matter how much I try, I can't believe it.
I wanted to see if I could bring myself to believe it if I got drunk,
So, I ended up drinking two whole jars.
But, I still can't believe it at all.
Hyo Seon.
Don't do it.
Don't do it!
- Hyo Seon.
- I said don't do that!
You won't even let me rely on you,
Why are you even taking away my alcohol.
Oppa...
Get lost.
I said to get lost!
You get lost,
and take Eun Jo too.
The export order... I was against it.
But, Eun Jo insisted.
If it weren't for Eun Jo, Dad wouldn't have done it.
No matter whatever Eun Jo said, Dad always...
No matter how many spiteful words Eun Joo said,
Dad trusted her like a fool.
If it weren''t for Eun Joo, dad wouldn't have become like this.
It wasn't Eun Joo, but
it was me.
I did that.
That evil bitch.
I'll kill her.
I won't let her get away with this.
Let's send Ahjussi off properly.
Right now,
let's just think about sending him off well.
Hyo Seon.
He can't go like this, Oppa.
To where... And how can I send Dad off?
I can't even believe that I'm wearing these kinds of clothes right now.
So how are you telling me to send Dad off when I don't know where he's going, Oppa?!
Noona.
I have a lot to do.
I have to go to the factory,
and I don't know when the last time I went to the research lab was.
Get ahold of yourself.
Let me go.
I have to go to the factory.
Get ahold of yourself!
You need to come to your senses and do what needs to be done.
Greet the guests and negotiate burial preparations with the elders.
There are too many things you have to do.
Ahjumma only cries.
Joon Soo's little noona has disappeared and I don't know where she is...
No one's in their right mind now.
Noona.
Dae Seong True Wine Makers and President Goo Dae Seong's funeral are all a mess.
Are you going to leave it like that?
The funeral of President Goo Dae Seong of Dae Seong True Wine Makers
That's right.
The funeral of President Goo Dae Seong of Dae Seong True Wine Makers.
Yes.
Condolences
You're coming to your senses now, right?
He's waiting for you...
If it's a relationship like ours, one phone call (In Japanese)
is enough to be the same as signing a contract.
But still, let's formally put this on a document and each get one copy.
It'll be like a contract,
but won't it's contents be more like
our companies sending love letters?
Your skills are really good, Hyung.
Hyung Gi Jeong.
Miss Miura, something suddenly came up.
I'll take care of it and call you back.
You're here? It's a bit earlier than our scheduled time.
Have a seat.
I ... didn't intend that.
Though I'm sure you won't believe me.
My goal was to make sure you didn't get Dae Seong True Winemakers.
I had no intentions of taking over Dae Seong True Winemakers.
After taking it instead of you,
I was going to return it to them.
Because of me,
do you know what happened?
Do you know what you've done to me?
I brought you came here just to talk business peacefully..
Stop looking at Dae Seong now.
Don't do anything! I won't let you do anything.
Are you saying that after you've thought of everything you've done?
Sit down.
Why did you do that
to my mom?
When my mom came and asked to see me just once,
why did you make my mom who couldn't run, run?
Who said that?
Did Father say that?
Why did you do it? Did you need to do that?
I've tried thinking about it from your perspective.
Since your mom hurt because of my mom,
I thought if I were you, I would also dislike my mom.
Since my mom even had me, he must hate my mom.
Just like me, I believed that both of you hyungs suffered.
Like that...
Did you want to re-chew memories that don't even exist?
Stop it right now.
No matter how much you disliked her, how could a person do that to another person?
That isn't something you should've done!
What else could I do? She knew I was hiding you.
I ran because I was sick of it.
The one who chased me until the end was your mother.
I didn't tell her to run.
You knew it would take a toll on my mom to run, but you didn't stop.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Are you implying I ran on purpose?
I did, too. Because of you.
I wanted to get something first so it wouldn't go to you,
and someone died as a consequence.
Just like I can't forgive myself, I can't forgive you.
Now, I really can't go back to before.
It's because of you.
I'm so grateful that I'm going crazy.
Dae Sung True Winemakers won't die.
You must hope that everything gets destroyed as it disintegrates into the air.
I'm sure you want to become the only seller in the rice wine market, without any competitors!
But that won't happen.
Give it up.
Don't do anything to Dae Seong True Winemakers.
If you do,
I won't just stay still.
If you don't stay still, what will you do?
I'm going to take you
and die together.
Mom!!
Joon Soo, go outside and play.
Tell the kitchen ahjummas to give you some cinnamon punch, have it before you play.
Because I can't visit you one by one, I apologize for making all of you walk this far to gather here instead.
After the funeral, I had a few immediate things to take care of,
so I lacked a lot of time.
Regarding the incident in Japan last time,
thanks to an influential person who had connections with Hyo Seon,
we were able to sell half of the containter's content in our shipment to Japan to the Japanese market.
The remaining half of the shipment was brought back and taken care of by Dae Seong True Winemakers.
What you mean, taken care of by Dae Seonng True Winemakers?
In Japan, we took care of the sales as an ingredient for vinegar.
And I drank
the remaining half.
If it were as promised, this is a time for me to start repaying you all for the money you've loaned us,
but apologetically, I am unable to do that at this time.
However, because Dae Seong True Winemakers has strong roots,
I am certain we will be able to regain our reputation from before.
You all trusted this point,
and thus lent us what was to many of you, your entire life's savings.
If you please just wait a little more,
Hyo Seon and I will work together to repay you as soon as possible.
If we can't wait any longer, what are you going to do?
Of course, I would like to wait for you until the end,
if only Dae Seong hadn't such a poor reputation.
I could wait for it, whether that be two years or three years.
However, how can I trust you young ones?
I heard that you were able to get profits on at least half the exports to Japan.
With that, I need to take care of urgent matters.
Hey, are you the only ones with urgent issues?
Who here doesn't have urgent circumstances, that you would be the one to claim those?
Of course. You shouldn't be the one to claim that.
Hyung-nim, if you say such things, it upsets me.
How could you say that knowing my circumstances-
Who are you to raise your voice in front of your elders?
What do you mean, raise my voice?
- I am only-
- Cut it out!
What measures are you going to take?
Don't you have some sort of plan?
We will give you shares proportionate
to your loans to Dae Seong True Winemakers.
All of you here will become owners of Dae Seong True Winemakers.
If you all will take responsibility for the success of Dae Seong True Winemakers.
our late
our late... President Goo Dae Seong will also be happy.
Small Noona!
- What?
- Let's play.
Let's play later.
Let's play right now.
Play with Big Noona.
Big Noona is a person who doesn't play with Joon Soo.
Little Noona is a person who plays with Joon Soo a little bit.
Mom won't play with me most of the time.
Dad always plays with Joon Soo.
Why won't Dad come back?
Huh? Why isn't Dad back?
Noona, there are lots of rocks there.
Sure. Can you get one for me too?
I'm curious about something.
I thought that you
had actually liked Dad quite a bit.
But you didn't shed a tear,
From the kitchen granny and all the staff,
there wasn't a single person who didn't cry.
How can you do that?
What is it that you're curious about?
Weren't you being sincere in front of Dad?
Do you think I'll answer that question?
Tell me.
Did you have any sincerity for my dad at all?
Why? What?
What are you looking at?
- What's sincerity?
- What?
What does this thing called sincerity mean exactly?
Is it nothing to you that my dad passed away?
How can you be so stoic? How can this be nothing?
If it weren't for you, this wouldn't have happened, Unni!
So what?
What?
So what is it you want me to do?
Now that I think about it, it seems like you're saying your dad died because of me.
- What should I do?
- What should you do?
If I tell you to do something, can you actually do it?
Can you do anything?
Then bring my dad back to life.
Bring my dad back to life!
Because I miss him to death, bring my dad back to life!
How could this happen?
It's terrible.
It doesn't make sense. It really doesn't make any sense.
I'm scared, Unni.
I'm scared to death.
It feels like I'm standing outside not wearing anything.
I'm cold...
and I'm scared.
Unni.
Don't cry.
Don't cry, Hyo Seon.
Until when are you going to keep on crying?
The elders say they don't need either stocks or shares. They're demanding that we repay their money immediately,
We have to give them money now.
The last of the yeast that your father made is all gone now.
We have to solve this yeast issue by ourselves now.
And I don't have confidence to produce wine that tastes the same way it did when your father made it.
There's still so much to take care of.
Why is it that all you do is cry every day?
Even if it's just once,
can't you comfort me?
Noona, rocks!
Even now, since I'm scared and lonely, I want you Unni
to cherish me at least a little,
then I'll feel like I'll be less scared..
Okay?
I'm so sick and tired of your whining, you idiot!
Please stop, I'm begging you!
Evil witch! I'm telling Dad...
What are you all doing right now?
Why have you all given up?
It's the middle of a work day, but why is everyone like this?
Is it all right for you to be acting this way now that the President is no longer with us?
What is this?
Aren't you going to work?
Is there anything for us to do now?
- What?
- There is no work for us.
There aren't any orders, what work are we supposed to do?
I'm going to make the yeast. So, please get ready.
- Will you be able to make the yeast?
- What do you mean?
And who'll examine the yeast after?
Are you saying now that I won't be able to make the yeast
because there's no one to test it?
I'm asking what you're doing!
Why are you all like this, really?!
Even when the factory and winery were both in trouble,
we still paid every single penny of your salary.
Are you saying you're not going to work even though you're getting paid as normal?
If you don't want to work, then quit immediately!
It's okay.
Do you think the ahjussies won't feel the loss?
Because President has left us, they're feeling low.
There's no need to push them like that.
Learn some things from Hyo Seon. To become kind and cheerful.
Hyo Seon is very good at not hurting other people's feelings.
Take a look at this.
Do you remember the trash-filled dumpling scandal?
Back then, there was a small business unfairly involved,
The company got embroiled and went bankrupt even before the real facts were confirmed.
Later, that company was found to be innocent,
but the articles that spoke of its innocence were only a few.
Let's draw parallels between that incident and our company problem and make a plea to the media.
Write something. Because I'm good at reading, I don't have a talent for writing.
If you write it, I'll review it.
Are you listening?
Starting tomorrow, you should know that we will not be coming to work.
Manager Kim, what do you mean by saying that?
This is the company, and we know we are your subordinates,
but, we're still your elders!
What on earth have you learned from the President?
Once in a while, he yelled at us for not doing things the way he liked.
But he never hurt our dignity.
We can't work here while being treated this way by someone young enough to be our daughter.
You know that now. Let's get going.
Manager Kim! Ahjussi!
Ahjussies!
Hyo Seon is here.
Joon Soo is here.
We're back.
Joon Soo, let's go wash our hands.
Where did you take a kid who has a cold?
Do you know how long I was looking for him?
If you were going to take him out, you should have told me.
Okay, Mom.
I just thought you were sleeping.
What on earth are you going to do if Joon Soo's cold gets worse?!
Hurry come in!
I'll help him wash up! I also have to wash up anyway!
We're done. It feels good, right?
Here we go.
Mom, I'll help him wash up.
Get away!
Let's go.
Is this it? This is what you're doing to me?
In the end, you made me a widow again.
You guys are crazy. You're out of your mind.
Did you guys make a bet
on how terrible this woman's fate can get through your hands?
Do you think I'll break down?
I'm Song Kang Sook!
If I break down, I will hang onto you and bring you down with me.
You think I'll go down alone?
Don't even think about it.
Mom.
Mom...
Mom, I was wrong.
I didn't know Joon Soo had a cold.
Don't touch me!
Just you try clinging onto me!
It disgusts me when you try clinging onto me. Got it?
♫ In the solictude which wakes me up ♫
♫ when I wake up from an exhausted sleep ♫
♫ because I still remember you smiling ♫
♫ I'm secretly smiling ♫
♫ Love leaves again this way ♫
♫ When the beautiful season arrives ♫
♫ In the sadness you left in the longing ♫
♫ I walk this street again ♫
♫ I am living day after day  ♫
♫ In your name when tears appear, ah  ♫
♫ I can't bear it  ♫
♫ So I can't laugh ♫
♫ I'll call out your name again ♫
♫ I'm living life recklessly ♫
♫ When I yearn for love again ♫
Read after you finish your food.
I told you to finish eating first.
♫ I am living day after day  ♫
Mom.
Chew well before you swallow, Joon Soo. Don't get sick anymore.
You must not get sick, okay?
Yes.
♫ I can't bear it  ♫
♫ So I can't laugh ♫
Article Submission
♫ I'll call out your name again ♫
Submitted by Goo Eun Jo, Dae Seong True Winemakers
Your words are too fierce.
It's convincing enough if you just calmly lay out the facts.
People will get fed up reading something excessively emotional like this.
Excessive?
- Did you just say excessive?
- Yes.
I'm someone who completely stands on Dae Seong Co.'s side,
but even I got fed up after reading a couple of lines.
No publications would accept this kind of article.
Write it again.
Where are you going?
Explain to me exactly how it's excessive, line by line.
Right now, persuading them is more important than giving you an explanation.
I failed to persuade the ajusshis.
After you've re-written it, go to the ahjussies, kneel down and beg them for their forgiveness while rubbing your hands.
Are you crazy? Why would I beg them?
- I haven't done anything wrong.
- You didn't do anything wrong?
I don't need people who get paid to just play around either. I'll just hire new people.
If it's so easy, then do it.
They're workers who have accumulated experience at Dae Seong Co. for more than 20 years.
If there are people who can replace them, then do it!
Go ahead and try.
I'd like to look at this one.
How could you...?
I wasn't able to offer my condolences. I've come too late.
You can see Dae Seong in every corner.
This winery reflects Dae Seong's character exactly.
Please leave. It's not right for you to be here.
Let me sample some free wine.
Hurry up and just say what you came here to say.
Give me back my money.
Didn't you take my money to buy rice? Give me back that money immediately.
It's not possible now.
- Then, I'll take the winery.
- Father.
Where is that girl that's working on developing the yeast? Can I see her?
I heard that you gave Ji Seong a piece of your mind.
He said you acted as if you were the gatekeeper
to protect Dae Seong True Winemakers from now on.
Is that really true?
What's the point of protecting Dae Seong Co. when it's already done for?
I‘ll pay a little more to what they owe me, so tell them to just give me the winery.
Thinking Dae Seong True Winemakers without Dae Seong means little,
I was just going to give it up,
but as I looked around the factory and winery...
I realized I must have it.
Pay the money back by next month.
You can give me Dae Sung Do Ga instead of money.
It's too much money for us to handle. We won't make it by next month. Please give us more time.
It's also too much for me to handle.
You turned your back on me, so I must get my money back at least.
Father.
You are groveling right now.
It would be best for you to just give up.
I asked the savings bank to see if the repayment period can be extended.
They said it's impossible.
What if we can't pay it back, do we have to hand over the winery?
Yes, since the president used the winery as collateral.
And now, we can't even go to any of our relatives in the family to ask for help.
What are we going to do?
I'll get things arranged somehow.
I'll try to get it somehow.
Why would you?
What does this have to do with you?
Do you have to talk like that?
What?
- Give me the money.
- I don't know what money you want me to give you?!
I'm sure you have the money that ahjussi Jang gave back,
Take out all the money you've hidden away all these years.
There is no such thing, little bitch!
- There isn't?
- No.
- There really isn't?
- I said there isn't!
- You're lying!
- You really...
There's no way you wouldn't have any money! Hyo Seon's dad
never cared where and how you spent his money.
There's no way you didn't put your hand in an open wallet.
You think I don't know you, Mom? How much did you take?
Take out all the money you've hidden!
You've gone crazy, haven't you?
Even if I did, what about you, me and Joon Soo's future?
Do you think I'll dump money on a failing company just like that?
I'll pay it back with interest!
- You really must be my daughter, judging from your bluffs.
- Hand it over!
It's dirty money I exchanged for my dirty fortune.
What right do you have to tell me give you that money?
- I won't give it to you! I can't give it to you!
- Mom!
- Let go of me.
- I said let go of me.
- Mom, please give it to me!
Hey. Get away from me, you bitch!
Don't open your mouth in front of me. Don't say a single word.
Don't touch me. Just try to speak a word to me.
Is that how it was?
Mom...
Is that what Mom was doing?
It's a lie, right?
I must not have heard correctly, right?
Are you just looking at me like that because my words don't seem like words to you?
I told you to pack your things! What are you still doing?
But, why are you... suddenly?
Madam, if there's something we did wrong, please tell us.
I don't want to listen to you, so leave.
Call me once you've packed your things. I'll pay you up to today's workday.
Madam...
What are we going to do?!
Grandmother!
Ahjumma! Where are you going?
Where are you going?
Baby, you have to live well. Okay?
What are you saying? Why are you leaving?
Oh our baby, we're going to miss you a lot.
Mom.
Grandmother Kkotnim and ahjumma... They weren't just employees working for us.
They're practically family to us.
Grandmother Kkotnim has been here since I was born and,
when my mom got sick and couldn't take care of me,
Grandmother was like a mom to me.
Mom, I need Grandmother here.
I can't live without Grandmother.
Leave with her then.
If that Grandmother is your mom, you should go and follow your mom.
Mom.
You sure have a lot of moms.
If you're going to snivel, leave.
Mom.
I don't know why you're treating me like this all of a sudden.
Stop acting like a victim.
You've lived like a princess so far, but that should be enough. It's time to stop now.
Mom.
I said stop crying in front of me, and leave!
Aren't you going to leave?
Grandmother and Ahjumma aren't leaving.
I've taken them to Do Ga.
There's a lot of work to be done there. All the ahjussies have left.
Mom...
Why is Mom treating me like this all of a sudden?
Why did she turn into a different person all of a sudden?
She hasn't become a different person all of a sudden.
Mom has been always like that. Didn't you know?
You're not the princess of this household anymore.
You can get chased out of here in your bare feet if you make the wrong move.
My mom is someone who will leave you like that.
She...
She can kick me out?
Don't you think she can do it? Our mom?
To me?
Why?
Come to your senses, Goo Hyo Seon.
I really beg of you to come to your senses and act at least a bit smart,
instead of crying all day like an idiot.
Find a way for you to live successfully,
in this household where nobody will take your side. Okay?
Get up.
Get up! Hurry up!
But... What are you talking about?
The person who killed Joon Soo's dad is you. Hyo Seon's uncle.
W-wh-what does that mean?
What? What is that?
What do you mean what is it?
You ruined Do Ga with your adulterated alcohol,
Only the one who died while running around to revive the bankrupt winery is pitiful.
With what kind of conscience are you continuing to live in this house?
Starting tomorrow, I don't want to see your face in this house anymore. Do you understand?
I'm calling you because I thought of a good plan.
What do you think about this, Father?
I'm thinking about putting all my shares of Hong Joo Ga on the market.
What?
I'll release my shares of Hong Joo Ga.
Then I'll sell them and use that money to repay our debt with you.
What do you think of that idea?
You crazy fool.
Sunbaenim....
Are you related to Hong Joo Ga?
Isn't Hong Joo Ga our country's greatest...
No, I'm not. You misheard.
Didn't you say you had shares of Hong Joo Ga?
I said you misheard.
Have a taste.
What are you doing all of a sudden without any reason whatsoever?
Just taste it.
How is it?
What?
Whose alcohol is it?
It's Dad's alcohol whose else?!
Are you sure?
What are you doing now?!
Are you sure? Are you sure...
It's your father's wine, right?
How ridiculous.
I made it.
I...
I was afraid I couldn't...
I was afraid I couldn't make it.
You
made it?
You really made this?
I'm asking you.
Did you really make this?
Yes. I did it.
I did it again, Goo Hyo Seon.
Now, this will become the hope of Dae Seong True Winemakers.
Don't you think so?
What will you do now?
I've made such a huge contribution to Dae Seong True Winemakers.
What are you going to do?
At this rate,
everything will become mine, Goo Hyo Seon.
But still, will that be all right with you?
My mom is no ordinary person, and I'm her daughter
There's a chance that I may be worse than my mom
I'm better than my mom. I'm much smarter than her.
Don't let anything happen to you.
Even if you do, I won't save you.
I've clearly warned you.
Okay?
Noona.
Later...
Tell me later.
Don't follow me.
A new windstorm in the domestic makgeolli market
If I could turn back the time,
what moment should I turn back to?
I think about this every day.
Should I go back to eight years earlier?
I should have never set foot in this house,
And I should have dragged my mom out of here.
If not...
The day that person packed up and left...
Should I have woken up even just one hour earlier,
when it was dark,
and left permanently?
If not that either,
when you said we wouldn't take any more bulk orders,
instead of not listening to you,
should I have quietly
listened to what you said?
When should I go back to
so that this wouldn't have happened?
From where do I have to reset
so that
I won't commit any sins?
Please drink this.
I made it.
Hyo Seon said it tasted the same...
But, I want Fa...
Fa-Fath...
Fath...
I really want to be praised by my dad.
I'm so sorry.
Please forgive me, Dad.
I did wrong.
Dad...
I was wrong.
♫  where you can't hold me again  ♫
♫  I ask again about the way  ♫
♫  Saying I want to see you and hold you again  ♫
♫  While looking at heaven I'm praying  ♫
♫  It must be you  ♫
♫  I cannot be without you  ♫
♫  Like this for another day, month or year  ♫
♫  I don't mind even if I am hurt  ♫
♫  I don't mind even if my heart breaks  ♫
♫  Because, yes...  ♫